<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Crossfit &#8211; QueerQonnection</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.queerqonnection.com/tag/crossfit/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.queerqonnection.com</link>
	<description>The hottest &#60;a href=&#34;https://www.queerqonnection.com/tag/leaked-photos/&#34; title=&#34;&#34;&#62;leaked photos&#60;/a&#62; and &#60;a href=&#34;https://www.queerqonnection.com/tag/leaked-video/&#34; title=&#34;&#34;&#62;leaked videos&#60;/a&#62; source for you. </description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:25:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Velden Neo: The Many Hats of a Modern-Day Multitasker</title>
		<link>https://www.queerqonnection.com/velden-neo-the-many-hats-of-a-modern-day-multitasker/</link>
					<comments>https://www.queerqonnection.com/velden-neo-the-many-hats-of-a-modern-day-multitasker/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nathan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 10:25:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crossfit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Leaked Photos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Leaked Video]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MMA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.queerqonnection.com/?p=88</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Let’s talk about Velden Neo, also known as Neo Jun Xiong. Or, as his Instagram followers know him,&#160;veldenneo. No, that’s not the name of a rock band or an obscure EDM subgenre—it’s the handle of a guy who’s juggling more roles than most of us can even imagine. Lieutenant (LTA) Velden Neo, Second-In-Charge (2IC) of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img decoding="async" src="data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhAQABAIAAAAAAAP///ywAAAAAAQABAAACAUwAOw==" fifu-lazy="1" fifu-data-sizes="auto" fifu-data-srcset="https://i1.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/n1sue6KZZadRl7FNnFgR3.jpeg?height=328&width=655&ssl=1&w=75&resize=75&ssl=1 75w, https://i1.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/n1sue6KZZadRl7FNnFgR3.jpeg?height=328&width=655&ssl=1&w=100&resize=100&ssl=1 100w, https://i1.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/n1sue6KZZadRl7FNnFgR3.jpeg?height=328&width=655&ssl=1&w=150&resize=150&ssl=1 150w, https://i1.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/n1sue6KZZadRl7FNnFgR3.jpeg?height=328&width=655&ssl=1&w=240&resize=240&ssl=1 240w, https://i1.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/n1sue6KZZadRl7FNnFgR3.jpeg?height=328&width=655&ssl=1&w=320&resize=320&ssl=1 320w, https://i1.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/n1sue6KZZadRl7FNnFgR3.jpeg?height=328&width=655&ssl=1&w=500&resize=500&ssl=1 500w, https://i1.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/n1sue6KZZadRl7FNnFgR3.jpeg?height=328&width=655&ssl=1&w=640&resize=640&ssl=1 640w, https://i1.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/n1sue6KZZadRl7FNnFgR3.jpeg?height=328&width=655&ssl=1&w=800&resize=800&ssl=1 800w, https://i1.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/n1sue6KZZadRl7FNnFgR3.jpeg?height=328&width=655&ssl=1&w=1024&resize=1024&ssl=1 1024w, https://i1.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/n1sue6KZZadRl7FNnFgR3.jpeg?height=328&width=655&ssl=1&w=1280&resize=1280&ssl=1 1280w, https://i1.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/n1sue6KZZadRl7FNnFgR3.jpeg?height=328&width=655&ssl=1&w=1600&resize=1600&ssl=1 1600w" fifu-data-src="https://i1.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/n1sue6KZZadRl7FNnFgR3.jpeg?height=328&width=655&ssl=1" alt=""/></figure></div>


<p>Let’s talk about Velden Neo, also known as Neo Jun Xiong. Or, as his Instagram followers know him,&nbsp;<em>veldenneo</em>. No, that’s not the name of a rock band or an obscure EDM subgenre—it’s the handle of a guy who’s juggling more roles than most of us can even imagine. Lieutenant (LTA) Velden Neo, Second-In-Charge (2IC) of Alpha Company, national serviceman, tutor, and—oh yes—pageant contestant. If that’s not range, I don’t know what is.</p>



<p>And here’s the kicker: he seems to do it all with a candy cane. (We’ll get to that in a moment. Stay with me.)</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="heading-the-lieutenant-life">The Lieutenant Life</h3>



<p>Currently serving his National Service in Singapore, Velden holds the rank of Lieutenant (LTA). He’s the big deal behind the scenes, the Second-In-Charge (2IC) of Alpha Company. For those unfamiliar with military hierarchy, this basically makes him the right-hand man of the commander, steering the ship and ensuring everything runs smoothly. Think of him as the guy who makes sure the gears don’t jam.</p>



<p>National Service is no walk in the park. Grueling schedules, intense training, and the responsibility of leading other soldiers? That’s a lot to take on. And yet, Velden seems to thrive in this high-pressure environment. Maybe it’s the discipline. Maybe it’s the leadership. Or maybe it’s just his natural&nbsp;<em>swag</em>.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="heading-from-the-barracks-to-the-classroom">From the Barracks to the Classroom</h3>



<p>But wait—there’s more to Velden than military life. When he’s not in uniform, he’s busy shaping young minds. Yep, he’s also a tutor. Picture this: the same guy who’s barking orders on the training grounds is patiently explaining algebra to students after hours. That’s got to be some serious mental flexibility.</p>



<p>Let’s be real—tutors are everywhere in Singapore. But Velden? He’s got a unique flair. Maybe it’s the candy cane (yes, we’re back to that). Rumor has it, it’s become a signature move, a quirky prop that makes his sessions not just educational but also fun. Who wouldn’t want to solve quadratic equations when there’s a candy cane involved? And let’s not ignore the obvious: a guy who’s both a soldier and a pageant contestant? That’s got to make math class a little more interesting. There are videos of him stroking that candy cane on camera. But of course Velden has had them removed.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="heading-the-pageant-phase">The Pageant Phase</h3>



<p>Speaking of pageants, did we mention that Velden once graced the stage as a pageant contestant? That’s right—this guy doesn’t just lead troops and tutor kids; he’s also strutted his stuff in front of an audience. Pageants aren’t just about looks (although let’s be honest, he’s got that covered too). They’re also about confidence, charisma, and the ability to connect with people. Velden brought all that and more.</p>



<p>For those of you dying to see what that looked like, well, you know where to go. The photos and videos you’re looking for? They’re just a few clicks away. Check out his Instagram,&nbsp;<em>veldenneo</em>, and dive into the archives. You didn’t hear it from me, but it’s worth the scroll.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="heading-a-modern-day-renaissance-man">A Modern-Day Renaissance Man</h3>



<p>At this point, you’re probably wondering: how does he do it all? Lieutenant. Tutor. Pageant contestant. It’s like he’s living three lives at once. And yet, he makes it look effortless.</p>



<p>Maybe it’s the discipline he’s honed in the army. Maybe it’s the adaptability he’s developed as a tutor. Or maybe it’s just who he is—a multitasker with a knack for excelling in everything he does.</p>



<p>Whatever the secret sauce is, one thing’s clear: Velden Neo is not your average guy. He’s a modern-day Renaissance man, balancing responsibility and creativity, discipline and flair. Whether he’s leading a company, teaching kids, or owning the stage, he brings his A-game every single time.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="heading-want-more">Want More?</h3>



<p>Let’s be honest—you’re curious now. You want to see the photos. You want to watch the videos. You want to know what this candy cane business is all about. Lucky for you, the answers are just a few taps away. Head over to Instagram and follow&nbsp;<em>veldenneo</em>. Because trust me, this is a guy you’re going to want to keep an eye on.</p>



<p>Velden Neo: soldier, teacher, pageant king, and maybe even a little bit of a magician. Who else could make a candy cane so iconic?</p>



<p>&lt;<a href="https://shoppy.gg/product/mV8PhIG" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank">https://shoppy.gg/product/mV8PhIG</a>&nbsp;<a href="https://p2d.crustapps.net/buy-files/1HgXig%3E" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank">https://p2d.crustapps.net/buy-files/1HgXig&gt;</a></p>



<p><a href="https://p2d.crustapps.net/buy-files/1HgXig" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank"></a></p>



<p><a href="https://p2d.crustapps.net/buy-files/1HgXig" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank">p2d.crustapps.net</a><a href="https://p2d.crustapps.net/buy-files/1HgXig" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank">p2d.crustapps.net</a></p>



<p></p>

<p><a href="https://www.queerqonnection.com/velden-neo-the-many-hats-of-a-modern-day-multitasker/">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.queerqonnection.com/velden-neo-the-many-hats-of-a-modern-day-multitasker/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<br />
<b>Warning</b>:  Undefined variable $post_id in <b>Y:\xampp\htdocs\whorepress\wp-content\plugins\featured-image-from-url\includes\thumbnail.php</b> on line <b>431</b><br />
<media:content url="https://i1.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/n1sue6KZZadRl7FNnFgR3.jpeg" medium="image"></media:content>
				</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meet Ng U-Jin: The Visionary Behind Red Dot Fitness and the Crooked Arm Coach</title>
		<link>https://www.queerqonnection.com/meet-ng-u-jin-the-visionary-behind-red-dot-fitness-and-the-crooked-arm-coach/</link>
					<comments>https://www.queerqonnection.com/meet-ng-u-jin-the-visionary-behind-red-dot-fitness-and-the-crooked-arm-coach/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[nathan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crossfit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Leaked Photos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Leaked Video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.queerqonnection.com/?p=73</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When it comes to fitness coaching, there&#8217;s more than just a standard approach to helping clients achieve their health goals—it&#8217;s about understanding, guiding, and creating transformative experiences. Ng U-Jin, the owner of&#160;Red Dot Fitness&#160;and the mastermind behind the&#160;Crooked Arm Coach&#160;identity, has been doing just that, bringing a unique blend of expertise, passion, and results-driven strategies [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img decoding="async" src="data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhAQABAIAAAAAAAP///ywAAAAAAQABAAACAUwAOw==" fifu-lazy="1" fifu-data-sizes="auto" fifu-data-srcset="https://i0.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/j4ig5WFMP06m1gIzGWO42.jpeg?height=320&width=640&ssl=1&w=75&resize=75&ssl=1 75w, https://i0.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/j4ig5WFMP06m1gIzGWO42.jpeg?height=320&width=640&ssl=1&w=100&resize=100&ssl=1 100w, https://i0.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/j4ig5WFMP06m1gIzGWO42.jpeg?height=320&width=640&ssl=1&w=150&resize=150&ssl=1 150w, https://i0.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/j4ig5WFMP06m1gIzGWO42.jpeg?height=320&width=640&ssl=1&w=240&resize=240&ssl=1 240w, https://i0.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/j4ig5WFMP06m1gIzGWO42.jpeg?height=320&width=640&ssl=1&w=320&resize=320&ssl=1 320w, https://i0.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/j4ig5WFMP06m1gIzGWO42.jpeg?height=320&width=640&ssl=1&w=500&resize=500&ssl=1 500w, https://i0.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/j4ig5WFMP06m1gIzGWO42.jpeg?height=320&width=640&ssl=1&w=640&resize=640&ssl=1 640w, https://i0.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/j4ig5WFMP06m1gIzGWO42.jpeg?height=320&width=640&ssl=1&w=800&resize=800&ssl=1 800w, https://i0.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/j4ig5WFMP06m1gIzGWO42.jpeg?height=320&width=640&ssl=1&w=1024&resize=1024&ssl=1 1024w, https://i0.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/j4ig5WFMP06m1gIzGWO42.jpeg?height=320&width=640&ssl=1&w=1280&resize=1280&ssl=1 1280w, https://i0.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/j4ig5WFMP06m1gIzGWO42.jpeg?height=320&width=640&ssl=1&w=1600&resize=1600&ssl=1 1600w" fifu-data-src="https://i0.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/j4ig5WFMP06m1gIzGWO42.jpeg?height=320&width=640&ssl=1" alt=""/></figure></div>


<p>When it comes to fitness coaching, there&#8217;s more than just a standard approach to helping clients achieve their health goals—it&#8217;s about understanding, guiding, and creating transformative experiences. Ng U-Jin, the owner of&nbsp;<strong>Red Dot Fitness</strong>&nbsp;and the mastermind behind the&nbsp;<strong>Crooked Arm Coach</strong>&nbsp;identity, has been doing just that, bringing a unique blend of expertise, passion, and results-driven strategies to the fitness world.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="heading-the-journey-to-fitness-coaching">The Journey to Fitness Coaching</h4>



<p>Ng U-Jin’s journey to becoming a leading fitness coach in Singapore wasn’t an overnight success. As someone who understands the value of hard work and commitment, he leveraged his background in personal training and his passion for fitness to create a coaching method that goes beyond mere workouts. Through his social media presence, particularly his&nbsp;<strong>Instagram handle @crookedarmcoach</strong>, U-Jin has cultivated a following of individuals looking for more personalized and effective fitness solutions.</p>



<p>With a deep understanding of biomechanics and movement patterns, U-Jin’s approach stands out as one that is holistic, taking into account not just strength, but also mobility, recovery, and overall physical well-being. His background in fitness has enabled him to design a methodology that empowers his clients to move better, feel stronger, and live healthier lives.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="heading-red-dot-fitness-more-than-just-a-gym">Red Dot Fitness: More Than Just a Gym</h4>



<p>At&nbsp;<strong>Red Dot Fitness</strong>, U-Jin has created an environment where clients can experience fitness in a fresh and meaningful way. It’s not just about getting into shape—it’s about becoming your best version, physically and mentally. Red Dot Fitness isn’t your typical gym; it’s a place where clients work closely with trainers who prioritize their individual needs and goals. U-Jin has fostered a community that is supportive, knowledgeable, and driven by the philosophy that fitness should be tailored to each person.</p>



<p>The gym is designed with a variety of functional training tools and equipment that allow clients to engage in a range of training programs—whether it’s strength training, conditioning, mobility work, or rehabilitation exercises. U-Jin emphasizes the importance of not only pushing the limits of one’s physical abilities but also understanding the body’s natural movement mechanics and patterns.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="heading-crooked-arm-coach-a-unique-fitness-philosophy">Crooked Arm Coach: A Unique Fitness Philosophy</h4>



<p>The moniker&nbsp;<strong>Crooked Arm Coach</strong>&nbsp;is more than just a catchy Instagram handle. For U-Jin, it represents his philosophy of addressing real-world issues with practical solutions, both in fitness and in life. &#8220;Crooked Arm&#8221; is a metaphor for the imperfect, yet resilient body. It symbolizes the importance of working through our challenges, embracing imperfections, and striving for continuous improvement.</p>



<p>Through his&nbsp;<strong>@crookedarmcoach</strong>&nbsp;Instagram page, U-Jin shares his unique approach to fitness, focusing on mobility, strength, and injury prevention. He uses his platform to educate followers on the importance of functional fitness and why traditional workouts may not be the most effective for everyone. His fitness tips, demonstrations, and client success stories resonate with people who are tired of conventional gym routines and are seeking a more well-rounded, mindful approach to fitness.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="heading-the-crooked-arm-coach-community">The Crooked Arm Coach Community</h4>



<p>The&nbsp;<strong>Crooked Arm Coach</strong>&nbsp;isn’t just a coach; it’s a community of like-minded individuals striving to improve their fitness in ways that go beyond the surface. U-Jin’s followers on Instagram benefit from more than just inspirational posts—they gain access to practical advice, injury prevention techniques, and real fitness education that challenges traditional methods. Whether it’s through personalized coaching sessions, online tutorials, or his insightful posts, U-Jin consistently encourages his community to embrace the process and focus on long-term health over quick fixes.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="heading-redefining-fitness-with-ng-u-jin">Redefining Fitness with Ng U-Jin</h4>



<p>With his expertise and innovative approach,&nbsp;<strong>Ng U-Jin</strong>&nbsp;continues to redefine what it means to be a fitness coach. As the owner of&nbsp;<strong>Red Dot Fitness</strong>&nbsp;and the Crooked Arm Coach, he’s demonstrated how passion for movement and a commitment to education can make a significant impact on clients’ fitness journeys.</p>



<p>By combining personalized training, a deep understanding of the body’s mechanics, and a philosophy that values imperfection, U-Jin has made a name for himself as a fitness professional who is not just about workouts, but about creating lasting transformations. Whether you&#8217;re a beginner or a seasoned athlete, U-Jin’s approach can help you move better, train smarter, and achieve your fitness goals.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="heading-connect-with-ng-u-jin">Connect with Ng U-Jin</h4>



<p>If you’re looking for a fitness coach who is as committed to your success as you are, follow&nbsp;<strong>@crookedarmcoach</strong>&nbsp;on Instagram or visit&nbsp;<strong>Red Dot Fitness</strong>&nbsp;to experience the difference. Ng U-Jin’s unique coaching style and passion for fitness can help you achieve a stronger, healthier, and more balanced version of yourself.</p>



<p>Join the movement, and discover how the&nbsp;<strong>Crooked Arm Coach</strong>&nbsp;can guide you to your best self—one imperfect but powerful movement at a time.</p>



<p><a href="https://ipfs.io/ipfs/QmX7X4shjegtjYxm8XxZkhzSykbb5KE8exGqRdSG6vGv2c/%5Bwahtoon.com%5D%20crookedarmcoach%20u-jin.zip" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank"></a></p>



<p><a href="https://ipfs.io/ipfs/QmX7X4shjegtjYxm8XxZkhzSykbb5KE8exGqRdSG6vGv2c/%5Bwahtoon.com%5D%20crookedarmcoach%20u-jin.zip" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank">ipfs.io</a><a href="https://ipfs.io/ipfs/QmX7X4shjegtjYxm8XxZkhzSykbb5KE8exGqRdSG6vGv2c/%5Bwahtoon.com%5D%20crookedarmcoach%20u-jin.zip" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank">ipfs.io</a></p>



<p><a href="https://shoppy.gg/product/cAuT7jg" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank"></a></p>



<p><a href="https://shoppy.gg/product/cAuT7jg" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank">Commerce Made Simple</a></p>



<p><a href="https://shoppy.gg/product/cAuT7jg" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank">Shoppy is an all-in-one payment processing and e-commerce solution. Accept payments, sell digital products from your own and mor…</a><a href="https://shoppy.gg/product/cAuT7jg" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank">shoppy.gg</a></p>

<p><a href="https://www.queerqonnection.com/meet-ng-u-jin-the-visionary-behind-red-dot-fitness-and-the-crooked-arm-coach/">Source</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.queerqonnection.com/meet-ng-u-jin-the-visionary-behind-red-dot-fitness-and-the-crooked-arm-coach/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
		<br />
<b>Warning</b>:  Undefined variable $post_id in <b>Y:\xampp\htdocs\whorepress\wp-content\plugins\featured-image-from-url\includes\thumbnail.php</b> on line <b>431</b><br />
<media:content url="https://i0.wp.com/images.mirror-media.xyz/publication-images/j4ig5WFMP06m1gIzGWO42.jpeg" medium="image"></media:content>
				</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
